（2016年）
（拉什维）
（人口1001人 成立于1885年）
（汽车旅馆）
都退下
Stand down!
都结束了 让他过去吧
It's over. Let him through.
哈尔呢
Where's Hal?
他在那间汽车旅馆
He's at the motel.
你需要医生吗
Do you need a doctor?
不用
No
你还好吗
You all right?
死了多少人
How many dead?
我还不清楚
I don't know yet.
但情况很糟
It's bad.
这么做真的值得吗
Was it worth it?
怎么了
What?
我也问了约翰同样的问题
It's the same thing I asked John.
守护者会怎么说
What will the Guardians say?
I failed to notify 'em,
我没通知他们
还让很多人有生命危险 还是出于…
and I put a lot of people's lives in danger for...
那些自私的理由
selfish reasons.
到时也不会有人反对任何法庭判我…
And that there won't be any pushback
in any court that convicts me
犯下鲁莽危害罪
of reckless endangerment.
正好能让他们俐落地解决掉烫手山芋
Kind of a nice,
clean solution to their problem...
也就是我
of me.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你早就警告过我
You told me.
是我坚持不离开
所以接下来无论发生什么事
I didn't leave town,
whatever happened next...
都算在我头上
was on me.
我知道
I know.
的确是
It is.
但我还是很难过自己说中了
But I can still feel bad about being right.
（2026年）
（施利茨啤酒）